Wait... without going through me—
Not on my watch!
Brute forcing your way into using
the shield's secret art...
You're a hell of a guy, Fate!
Fay?
Is that you, Fay?
It's been a while...
Lady Roxy.
Fay!
Please, get out of here quickly.
It won't be down for long.
I'll buy you some time.
Fay...
I'm sorry for lying to you all this time.
And thank you for everything, Lady Roxy!
Fay!
Fay...
It's already back up.
You didn't think it'd be that easy, did you?
Shut up! Let's do this, Greed!
Yeah! You should be able to use it now!
Right! I'm counting on you, partner!
Grand Cross Returnable!
Go!
Devouring
Now it's ensnared!
Fate!
That was clever.
Immobilizing the Divine Dragon
with some art I'd never seen before...
Now we can actually fight one-on-one.
He's pushing me back...
My stats must have dropped
from using that secret art!
There are three reasons.
One: By forcing your way into the
Domain of E, you're exhausted.
Two: You're devoting a portion of
your strength to maintaining that art.
And three...
I haven't gotten serious yet!
Got you!
Well, that was dangerous!
Stick close! Don't let him get any distance!
I know!
What a desperate offense.
Rushing headlong into your attacks...
Oh, I see.
If you get too far away, you won't
be able to maintain that art of yours.
Looks like I was right.
This isn't over!
Panicking now that I've seen through you?
A swing that wide leaves you wide open!
What a shame. I believe this is over.
Eris seemed to have high hopes for you...
But after all the trouble you've caused me,
you'll have to pay the price.
What?!
Illusion magic...?!
When did you—
I thought you'd let your guard down
once you were confident you'd won.
No... then you sacrificed your arm?!
It was an all-or-nothing gamble.
You can have my left arm.
Take it with you!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Where am I?
I think I've seen this before...
And after all the times
I tried to warn you...
You're... that girl that was Haniel's core.
My name is Luna. Thank you.
For what?
For killing me.
Don't look so sad.
I think it was for the best.
But... I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I can't do much more.
I'd been holding it back in here.
Then it was thanks to you that
the Gluttony skill had quieted down?
But not anymore.
I'm not able to support you.
Support...?
If you devour the Divine Dragon,
you'll lose control of yourself.
Then soon I'll...
I was wondering why you'd gone quiet.
So you were in here!
Greed?!
Don't stare.
We're running out of time. Gotta head back.
H-Hang on!
Thank you for the warning.
But I can't let the Divine Dragon
roam free without its master.
I'm going to slay it.
I see.
You're a real handful.
So, you used to be a person, huh?
Think of it as a temporary form.
You ready to do this?
Because we've got a rampaging
Divine Dragon to deal with!
I don't know how long I've got left.
We'll end this fast!
What's the plan? Kinda hard to use
a shield or bow with one arm.
Greed...
Oh, dammit, don't tell me—
You ever want to fly before?!
What the hell, Fate?!
Brawl Art: Ruinous Strike!
Treating me like a throwing weapon...
Come on, I got you back, didn't I?
Oh, this isn't over, pal.
Let's Identify this thing!
Ruler of the Skies
Divine Dragon
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Stamina Boost (Mega), Magic Boost  (Mega)
Spirit Boost (Mega), Health Regen Boost
I've got a slight edge in stats, but...
The Domain of E is the world of inhuman
strength. I wouldn't trust numbers too much.
In that case, let's focus on what we can do!
Not done yet!
Fate!
It's fine!
Sharp Edge enhanced with the Might skill
that doubles your strength!
This ends now!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Not yet...
Can't... let it take me yet.
If I go berserk now...
I'll become a bigger threat
than the Divine Dragon!
Before... that happens...
You... a-are you—?!
I can't... hold on much longer...
So before I'm lost...
Stop. Don't! Don't do this, Fate!
I'm sorry, Greed.
Accessing your new level has reset my stats.
Strength Boost (Low)
Strength Boost (Med)
Strength Boost (Large)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost  (Med)
Agility Boost (Med)
Health Regen, Health Regen Boost
Stamina Boost (Mega), Magic Boost  (Mega)
Spirit Boost (Mega)
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Conceal, Night Vision, Brawler,
Holy Sword Technique
One-Handed Sword Technique,
Two-Handed Sword Technique
Now, even if I go berserk...
the damage will be minimized.
In the end... the skill's devouring you, too?
I didn't think this day would come so soon.
Please...
Kill me, Myne.
If you push too hard, the skill overwhelms
you, making you lose control...
I warned you.
Sorry.
I understand.
I'll keep my promise.
No!
Lady Roxy...?
Why?
Are you seriously asking me that?!
What were you trying to do?!
Don't look at me.
I never wanted you to see me like this...
Lady Roxy?
Did you really think this would be enough
to make me hate you, Fay?!
No matter what power you wield,
you're still the Fay I know!
So... don't try to kill yourself.
It's so strange...
The Gluttony skill was rampaging before,
but it's quiet now.
Come.
Let's return to Babylon.
I was afraid... of her hating me.
But she still accepts me,
even after learning the truth.
I kept saying I wanted to save Lady Roxy...
But the truth is, I wanted her
to save me... like she did before.
You've found your support.
None for you!
Oh, would you pipe down?!
Where am I?
My room at the inn?
Right... Northern cut my left arm off.
It's already noon.
How long was I asleep?
A whole week.
Eris...!
Still worried about me?
Myne?
You sleep too much.
You can't blame him,
considering how overboard he went.
Here, you forgot this.
Greed!
You just now remembered
I was missing, didn't you?
O-Obviously not...
I have to say, you're looking pretty messy.
We had to go into the central
part of Galia to find him.
Why wouldn't he be dirty?
I seriously thought I wasn't
gonna make it back...
It was really far. A huge pain.
What was he doing over there?
I think a monster carried him away.
All because Myne forgot to collect him.
Myne...!
I was busy dealing with the other one.
What other one?
Envy.
It'd be a bad idea if he found
another vessel like Northern
and started causing trouble again.
Vessel? What was going on with
Northern and Envy, anyway?
He was just being controlled.
Like a puppet, really.
The one calling the shots
was the Black Gun-Sword, Envy.
Envy was in control?
Did you know that, Greed?
Nope. I had no idea
he could use mind control.
But considering how twisted he is,
it doesn't surprise me.
Mind control, huh?
We obviously couldn't just ignore that.
You went and destroyed him, right?
Weapons of Mortal Sin can't be destroyed.
What'd you do, then?
Threw him to the far side of Galia.
The most meat-headed solution possible...!
That aside, Fate.
After defeating the Divine Dragon,
you've proven your potential.
We'd like your help.
My help?
Well, the plan to manufacture a crowned
human with Roxy's death is over now.
Swear to me that you'll never go
after Lady Roxy again.
I'll hear you out after that.
Deal. Envy was the one who
came up with the idea, anyway.
And looking back now,
I was a fool to go along with it.
With the Divine Dragon gone,
the country will be entering a new era.
And we'll need your help
for what comes next.
That said, you're in no position to refuse.
This is something that all Skill of
Deadly Sin wielders have to deal with.
I don't know what you mean by all of that...
But since I was born with the Gluttony skill,
I think there must be some reason why.
And I want to know that reason.
But first... let's do something
about that arm.
Fix my arm?
I've never heard of magic like that before.
It's possible.
I'll have my arm back...?
With that settled, let's get out of here
before Roxy comes back.
Why?
It's dangerous for you
to be around her right now.
Just hearing her name was enough
to stir Gluttony, wasn't it?
Okay.
Come on, come on!
Keep those feet moving, Miria!
Hey, it's Raine!
What?! Where? Where is she?!
I got you!
Lady Roxy!
That was dirty, Miria!
Heading out, Lady Roxy?
Yes. Look after things while I'm away.
Sure! Have a good trip!
Bet she's going to see that bonehead again...
It's already been a week.
Hey there, step on up!
Look, Fay, I saw some grapes today and...
Fay?
Fay! Where are you?
Forgive me for suddenly
disappearing like this.
I'm sorry I never told you
about my Gluttony skill.
And... thank you.
I have to leave for now, but I promise
I will return to you, Lady Roxy.
Please, take care until that day.
Fate.
Struggling with something
like this by himself...
And when you were the one
who gave me so much courage.
You there!
It's dangerous to be wandering
about at this hour.
You need to run on home.
I-I'm sorry! Please don't hit me!
Hit you? Why would you think that?
B-Because I made a holy knight mad...
I was just giving you a warning!
I-I'm sorry!
The people really do fear
the holy knights, then...
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I... am ashamed to be a holy knight.
Wait a moment.
Here.
Okay, now once you finish eating,
head on home.
I'm sure your family is worried.
I don't have one. A family or a home.
But I'll get going.
Thank you for the sandwich!
Do you have somewhere to stay?
Nope. But now I know
the capital isn't all bad.
I'm real glad I met such a nice holy knight!
See ya!
Wait! What's your name?
Fate! Later!
See you later!
That was the moment I became able to hold my
head up and be proud of being a holy knight.
We will meet again, won't we?
I'll need to get stronger,
for when the day comes.
You'll see, Fay.
Then Corpse was Fate all along...
That's quite the shock, isn't it, Rafale?
Yes...
I have research left to attend to.
What exactly does he do during
all this research of his?
I'm glad you killed Hado...
Fate!
Take 40% of what I've got!
This is the secret art of my
4th level, Twilight Healing!
All right!
Looks like it worked.
I'll see you back at the capital.
I should get going, too.
We just got you a new scabbard, though!
Except that now you're an exceptional
warrior who's made it into the Domain of E.
So you need to have a sword to match!
So what? You're not satisfied with regular
whetstones? You need the fancy kind now?
Yep! I'm thinking a carbuncle
whetstone would be perfect.
A good reflection of how awesome I am.
And where are we supposed to
get the money for that?
If we don't have it now,
we've just gotta earn it!
I guess we do.
Let's do this, partner!
Yeah! Fight like the glutton you are!